[Music]
Hey friend, come quickly, I am getting time to go to the market,
hey, should I buy chicken today? Hey friend, I can't buy chicken, it is
very expensive, I always do this, I did
n't even care, oh my god, I have
spoiled your mood, shut up,
sit down
[Music] I pushed ahead,
but wait a second, daughter, wait, wait, wait, wait, I am
taking the Nagaman,
brother, look, look, you are
running, you are a fugitive, stop, stop, stop
[Music] Let me
bear this pain of love,
wow, what a scene it is,
play further
[Music]
Hey friend, you are laughing so much for the chicken, come on, give me the
chicken, I have brought the
chicken, wow, what a
smile, oh oh oh,
this was bound to happen